europebet.com 2018-11-15

# Privacy Policy

We at Europebet (a brand name of Chempionebi 111 Limited) understand that using any online service involves significant trust on your part. We value your trust and your custom and make it a high priority to ensure you are aware of the purposes for which we will use your personal information (“Personal Information”) and the measures we take to keep your data secure confidential. Personal Information is any information about you and may include your name and address, date of birth, payment card details and any other information you may wish to provide. Europebet will attempt to ensure that its use of your Personal Information is compliant with data protection and privacy regulations in the countries where we operate and the purpose of this Privacy Statement is to ensure that you are informed of our use of your Personal Information.

 **How is your Personal Information collected by Europebet?**  
 _  
Website:_  
We receive and store any Personal Information you enter on our website or give us in any other way, including via any App. You will be asked to provide your Personal Information for the purposes of registering with Europebet and opening an account with us.  
We automatically collect session information about your computer or hand held device when you visit this website or use our App(s). We use this automatic information to customize your user experience; to inhibit fraud; to serve advertisements, special offers and other information that may be of interest to you; and for other legitimate purposes we bring to your attention. For more information, please see our “Cookies Policy”.

Where you provide a telephone number within your Personal Information you consent to europebet contacting you by telephone to improve the services we offer to you and to let you know about special offers or to update you on your account with Europebet generally. We may record such calls for quality and training purposes.  
 _  
Social media:_  
If you make use of any Europebet social media features, either on our website, through an App or otherwise through a social media provider, we may access information about you via that social media provider in accordance with their policies.  
 _  
3rd parties:_  
We also may obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from affiliated entities, business partners and other independent third-party sources and add it to our account information. Examples of information we may receive include: contact information, purchase history, and demographic information. When we collect information about you from a third party, we ensure that appropriate consent has been obtained. By transacting on our website or through our Apps, you agree that we may collect such information for fraud prevention purposes.

 **How will we use your Personal Information  
**  
We use sensitive billing information (such as cardholder name, credit card number, and expiration date) for the purpose of providing you with our services on our website or through our App(s). We use other information about you for the following general purposes: to provide you with the products and services you request; maintaining our own accounts and records; to communicate with you in general; to respond to your questions and comments; monitoring website usage levels and quality of service; to measure interest in and improve our products, services, website and our Apps; to notify you about special offers and products or services that may be of interest to you; to otherwise customize your experience with this website or our Apps; to reward you as part of any reward and recognition program you choose to join; to solicit information from you, including through surveys; to resolve disputes, collect fees, or troubleshoot problems; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; to enforce our Terms and Conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection

 **Disclosing your Personal Information  
**  
Your Personal Information may, for the purposes described above, be transferred or disclosed by us to any associated company which is a member of our group of companies known as the Betsson Group or a business partner which is well placed to process your Personal Information for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement. We and these companies may from time to time retain third parties to process your Personal Information for the purposes and such processing will be governed by a contract in the form required by law. Where required by law or regulation your personal data may also be disclosed to an applicable governmental, regulatory or enforcement authority.

 **Consent  
**  
By providing your Personal Information and registering with us or logging on with us when you enter the website, you freely consent to Chempionebi 111 LLC processing and disclosing your Personal Information for the purposes and otherwise in the manner set out in this Policy. Only designated departments within the group will process to your personal data, such as Customer Service, Payments & Fraud, AML analyst and Compliance. If you wish to qualify, vary, modify or limit your consent in any way then please notify us using the details shown on the "Contact Us" pages of our Website.

 **General information  
**  
The Betsson Group includes all direct and indirect subsidiaries and related companies wherever located in the world as may exist from time to time.

In the event that the purposes for processing your Personal Information change, then we will notify you as soon as practicable and seek any additional consent that may be required.

For full details about Betsson Group members, where they operate or for a copy of your Personal Information or any other queries you may have about our data protection policy please contact Europebet. Again, our contact details are located in the "Contact Us" pages of our Website.
